You're probably really excited to get started,
你可能真的很开心,
but maybe you have a few questions,
但也许你有几个问题,
like what's a quant?
比如什么是量子？
And what does a quant do?
量子做了什么？
We were really lucky when building this nanodegree program.
在构建这个纳米级程序时，我们真的很幸运。
We got to work with some of the leading players in the quant world.
我们与量子世界的一些主要参与者合作。
To tell you a little more about that world,
为了更多地告诉你这个世界
we have Jonathan Larkin,
我们有量化股票策略师Jonathan Larkin。
a strategist in quantitative equities.
He's held senior positions in
他曾在几家主要金融机构担任高级股权交易的高级职位。
quantitative equity trading at several of the leading financial institutions.